you're going to see a video of Fran Rivera on
vas a ver un vídeo de Fran Rivera en
fadinger
fadinger
spenger why are you laughing I've been very
spenger por te ríes te lo he dicho muy
serious about it Hi everyone fadinger Hey but
en serio Hola a todos fadinger Oye pero
Hey good Setup good Setup eh watch eh how would
Oye buen Setup buen Setup eh ojo eh qué
a Setup like that be from
tal estaría un Setup así a partir de
now on like Hey listen to me Look it's
ahora en plan Oye pues escúchame Mira es
better than the one on the lne poor thing m
mejor que el de la lne pobrecita m
Sander pl okay let's put up a video of
Sander pl vale vamos a poner un vídeo de
Fran Rivera putting Pantoja really
Fran Rivera poniendo verdad la Pantoja
what's been this weekend
que sido este fin de semana
and what a good picture It's good that he
y vaya cuadro sea bueno Que bueno que
comes who are you going to defend
venga a quién vas a defender tú a
none How about none Marina let's
ninguno Cómo que a ninguno Marina es que
see it's good Put the video if you're
vamos a ver es que bueno Pon el vídeo si
going to put up a video of
es que vas a poner un vídeo de
tel yes it's modified because it's a
tel sí está modificado porque es un
YouTube channel that uploads it modified
canal de YouTube que lo sube modificado
but man we're going to have it not like
pero hombre ya la vamos a tener no como
none but if in this case it's very
que ninguno pero si aquí caso está
clear
clarísimo
you as a result of your
vosotros a raíz de de la muerte de tu
father's death it was never especially I mean
padre nunca fue especialmente o sea
when my father was there he was one
cuando estaba mi padre delante era una
person and when my father wasn't there he
persona y cuando estaba no estaba mi
was
padre era
another so when my father died
otra entonces cuando muere mi padre
obviously there was nothing to
evidentemente pues ya no había nada que
fear he made you look down on him a lot How does
temer os hacía muchos desprecios Cómo
your mother live through that moment  My mother was
vive tu madre ese momento a mi madre le
very hurt, eh, everything that happened and she was
dolió mucho eh todo lo que pasó y ella
left with
se quedó con
[Music]
[Música]
with the anguish of whether she did
con la angustia de que si hizo lo
enough for us to have
suficiente porque nosotros tuviéramos
my father's things, I don't remember my
las cosas de mi padre no recuerdo de mi
father's things, it's something that Francisco
padre es una cosa que Francisco ha
left for his children and
dejado para que sean para sus hijos y
sooner or later they have to be for
que tarde o temprano tienen que ser para
his children, it can't be for more. No one
sus hijos no puede ser para más nadie
has had any contact, any
has tenido algún contacto alguna
verbal communication with Isant, I don't
comunicación verbal con isant yo no
have anything to do with her, it's a
tengo por tener nada con ella un tema
lawyer issue and it's
abogados y es en
specifically a lot of memories
concreto muchos recuerdos
like Francisco's otar suits, capes,
como trajes de otar de Francisco capotes
crutches,
muletas
trophies, the parade, no, there aren't four left. Oh,
trofeos la parada no no quedan cuatro Ah
okay, do you want to say something about what you've
vale quieres decir algo sobre lo que has
seen so
visto hasta
far? I mean, look, Fran
ahora s quiero decir que mira Fran
Rivera is going to have his third
Rivera va a tener su tercer
child, he's surely in Japan, you've spent
hijo seguro que está en Japón has pasado
a couple of years in Japan. No, my hotel is in
un par de par en Japón No mi hotel es
Japan, they
japon
're the best, I mean, they're great
son los mejores o sea son unos cracks
with the self-service, the code, I don't
con el autoservicio de el código de No
know, well, well, they're, I don't know that you're not
sé bueno bueno son yo no sé que no lo
going to
vas a
show it, but of course. In exchange for what?
enseñar pero claro A cambio de qué
Because it's that, of course, eh, when there have to be
Porque es que claro eh cuando tiene que
2,000 likes because the truth is
haber 2000 likes porque es que de verdad
that the entrance is to piss myself, let's see,
que es que la entrada es para mearse a
I would give you like, let's see.  400
ver yo te daría like a ver faltan 400
likes are missing, I would give them, eh, are you going to show us
likes yo los daría eh nos vas a enseñar
the
al
[Laughs]
[Risas]
hotel really what to do? Yes.
hotel de verdad lo que hay que hacer sí
Ah, well, there's a word
Ah bueno es que hay una palabra que se
called Cartier Cartier and there's a, but no, no,
llama Cartier Cartier y Hay un pero no
no, eye, eye, I can't stop there. I
no no ojo ojo ahí no me puedo parar Yo
still don't count it, no, no, as soon as we
todavía no la cuenta no no en cuando
have 5,000 members,
tengamos 5000 miembros
yes, no, I'll stop there. It's that
sí no en tos ahí me paro en to es que
Cartier already has 10,000 members, 10,000
Cartier ya son 10000 miembros 10000
members, of course, let's see. I don't know why
miembros claro a ver no sé porque la
people today do
gente está hoy un
n't like us, they don't like us, we'll have to
poquito no nos quiere no nos quiere
leave, I don't know where, no, the
habrá que irse no sé a dónde ya no s el
next one, no, no,
próximo no s a
well, you can put collaborations with
bueno te puedes poner colaboraciones con
Loli below. There's nothing left if it doesn't
lolta más abajo Ya no hay nada si no te
go well with Loli, there's nothing further down.
va bien con Loli ya más abajo no hay
FR Rivera has
nada FR Rivera ha
said it for
dicho poror
years He's already told us, they've sold it to us
años Ya nos ha contado nos lo han
as a super testimony and he's been
vendido como un super testimonio y lleva
telling the same thing for 10 years It's like, Wow,
contando lo mismo 10 años Es como Wow
Fran Rivera surprises us, doesn't surprise us You're welcome, you've
Fran Rivera nos sorprende no nos
been telling us the
sorprende De nada nos llevas contando la
same story that it'll be true, I'm
misma historia de que será verdad yo
sure it'll be
estoy estoy segura que será
true, what the hell is that?  I'm
verdad qué es que yo estoy
completely sure it's true But
completamente seguro que es verdad Pero
come on no no but I'm also sure it's
vamos no no pero yo también estoy segura
true one thing he says let's see
que es verdad una cosa dice a ver por
please he says uh he says in front he had a
favor dice eh dice por delante tenía una
face in front of obviously from paqu and
cara delante de evidentemente de paqu y
behind him he despised us he says that we
por detrás nos despreciaba dice de que
made him two children of 7 10
que le hemos hecho dos niños de 7 10
years old for this and then he says and then there's
años para esto y luego dice y luego ya
nothing more to see like with
no hay más que ver en plan con los
his father's objects that when he died r that r that
objetos de su padre que cuando murió r
no that no that no Kiko Rivera
que r que no que no que no Kiko Rivera
supposedly Kiko Rivera supposedly had
supuestamente Kiko Rivera supuestamente
seen them I never thought I would talk
los había visto nunca pensé que hablaría
about Kiko Rivera in a trio of well the
de Kiko Rivera en un tría de biena la
surreal truth But but yes and then I'll
verdad surrealista Pero pero sí y luego
tell you another thing in what happens is that I
te digo otra cosa em lo pas es que yo
also understand that he's going to have a
también entiendo que va a tener un
third child and that he has to eat himself he
tercer hijo y que hay que comer él mismo
says Fran Rivero recognizes it and says I
dice Fran Rivero lo reconoce y dice yo
do this for money I do an
esto lo hago por dinero hago una
intervention every x time I feel like he
intervención cada x tiempo cojo siento
knows that he's not here save me that he's a
sabe que no está sálvame que está un
little safer the most similar thing is uh
poco más a salvo lo más similar es eh
There are two people and they're looking at me It's that
Hay dos personas y me están mirando Es
people are not used to
que la gente no está acostumbrada a
talking to or going to talk so clearly
hablar a o ir hablar tanto claro
eh And what are you talking about for seven of course
eh Y tú qué hablas para siete claro
um and and and that's it but let's say the guy is setting it
em y y y eso pero vamos que el tío se lo
up Well I don't know what they could have
monta Pues no sé que le habrán podido
paid him well 15,000 easily 15
pagar pues 15000 tranquilamente 15
20,000 but the thing is what they've told him what he's told he's already
20.000 pero es que lo que lo que le han
told 598 times exactly the same
contado 598 veces exactamente el mismo
testimony is very obvious it's very
testimonio es muy evidente es muy
obvious yes it's too obvious I don't
evidente sí es demasiado evidente no
think it's true But it is
liego que sea verdad Pero sí que es
true that for me on a journalistic level there
verdad que a mí ya a nivel periodístico
are already four or five against me and I already
ya son cuatro o cinco en contra y ya
miss something in my favor Honestly the way
echo de menos algo a favor Honestamente
things are So in the
las cosas como son Entonces como al
end Isabel Pantoja is left as
final es que queda Isabel Pantoja como
the great victim of everyone against her
la gran víctima de todos en su contra
Poor thing no, she's a little and as with
Pobrecita no que es un poco y como de
Isabel Pantoja we're never going to know her
Isabel Pantoja nunca vamos a saber su
version because we're not going to know it
versión porque no la vamos a saber a no
unless there's no money to pay
ser que no hay dinero para pagar a no
unless one day she does something to suum
ser que algún día haga algo a suum
meditate whiter more we're not going to we're never
medita más blanco más no lo vamos no
going to know her version
vamos a conocer jamás su versión a no
unless I don't know I don't know Carmina look at that you
ser que no sé No lo sé Carmina mira que
have her there on the screen What a
la tienes ahí en pantalla Qué mujer más
beautiful woman version her version is that she kept
bella versión su versión es que se quedó
things Marina there's no more Yes
las cosas Marina no hay más Sí es que
it seems to me dude because like  she
eso me parece tío por como que se las
kept them yeah Well there they were No, of course,
quedó sí Bueno ahí estaban No claro que
very strong but I do see it we're
muy fuerte pero yo sí lo veo estamos
talking about a woman who went to
hablando de una mujer que ha ido a la
jail because she collaborated with
cárcel porque ha colaborado con el
Julin Muoz This kid yeah yeah yeah no
Julián Muñoz Este chiqu sí sí sí no
well and the thing about the kiosk owner and a million
bueno y lo de la quiosquera y un millón
things is that in the end she is a person
de cosas es que al final es una personaa
of the era Well of
de laera
course she did that thing about Pirin of course
Pues claro que hizo eso de pirin claro
she said my son is the son of
esta dijo mi hijo es el más hijo de
Pirin of Pir Sorry my son is the
pirin de pir Perdón mi hijo es el más
son of Pakir And of course he had all that
hijo de pakir Y claro que tenía todo eso
And that can't be I mean he has other
Y eso no puede ser o sea tiene otros
children he has two other children that the
hijos tiene otros dos hijos que la la
father's will was that it be shared among
voluntad del padre era que se repartira
the three children Why the hell do
para los tres hijos Por qué tienes
you have everything in one room and Kiko Rivera has
tú en un cuarto todo y Kiko Rivera lo ha
told it there you have it, you have the proof that it
contado ahí tienes tú ya la la prueba de
's all true, look, it's not
que es verdad todo fíjate tampoco se
repeated that much no And look why are we
repite tanto no Y fíjate porque estamos
stopped eh Look that in addition
parados eh Fíjate que además
Fran always says that he has already told this before
siempre cuenta Fran que esto ya otra vez
that according to
lo ha contado que según le contaba
someone very close to him Pakirri told him but of course
alguien muy cercano pakirri pero claroo
we can't prove it either because
tampoco lo podemos probar porque
unfortunately Pakirri is not here he
desgraciadamente pakirri no está él al
apparently wanted to be, he was aware between
parecer se quería era consciente entre
quotes of what was happening with
comillas de lo que pasaba con respecto a
his two children and with other things and
sus dos hijos y respecto a otras cosas y
apparently he wanted to
al parecer se quería
divorce Isabel Pantoja And apparently he had
divorciar de Isabel Pantoja Y al parecer
always been in love with
siempre estaba había estado enamorado de
Carmina Well also seg precisely
Carmina Bueno también seg justamente
according to Rocio Carrasco to put
según Rocío Carrasco por poner
Died or rather according to Rocio Carrasco also
Murió o sea según Rocío Carrasco también
Rocio Jurado died in love with Pedro
Rocío Jurado murió enamorada de Pedro
Carrasco and then images were seen of
Carrasco y luego se vieron imágenes de
the or rather of course this this thing of the
las o sea claro este esto de la
perception of the children is also very
percepción de los hijos también es muy
uh subjective No but come on still and the whole
eh subjetiva No pero vamos aún y todo lo
issue of the objects is that they
del tema de los objetos es que me
seem really so cruel to me it's that we're no longer
parecen de verdad tan cruel es que ya no
talking about an economic value we're talking
hablamos de un valor económico hablamos
about an emotional value that happens to me and it does
de un valor emocional a mí me pasa eso y
n't have to run let's go into
no tiene para correr vamos me meto en
cantora Let's mean no no no no no I don't know I don't
cantora Vamos o sea no no no no no sé
lose coverage no no I don't put the video
no pierdo cobertura no no pongo el vídeo
okay okay okay It's nothing material there is no
vale vale valeas No es nada material no
material value there was a moment
hay un valor material hubo un momento
when he stopped fighting because I asked him
que dejó de luchar porque yo se lo pedí
because it was necessary to involve and
porque había que involucrar y había que
my grandfather Antonio Rivera had to be sued
demandar a mi abuelo Antonio Rivera
my uncles had to be sued and I said
había que demandar a mis tíos y yo dije
look it's been all nonsense
mira es que ha sido todo un sinsentido
an
un
absurdity and and there was a moment I say it
despropósito y y había un momento digo
seems  and my father only has one son I'm
parece y mi padre solo tiene un hijo le
going to give him the Christ of the
voy a hacer entrega del Cristo de las
Three Falls that his father carried
tres caídas que que su padre ha llevado
it's time for him to inherit this from
es el momento de que él herede esto de
his father because it's going to give him so much
su padre porque le va a dar muchísima
joy I know that down above he's going to
alegría Yo sé que el desde arriba va a
be proud that you have it he
estar orgulloso de que tú lo tengas ya
's a man now and he has to have it
es un hombre y tiene que tenerlo él
Of course my father's wishes were not respected at all he
Desde luego no se respetaron para nada
left everything
los deseos de mi padre que lo dejó todo
crystal clear they were not respected at all at
cristalino no se respetaron para nada n
all It's that your father would have
para nada Es que tu padre se hubiera
divorced if he had still been alive they
divorciado si hubiera seguido vivo a mí
tell me and they tell me that he was in the process
me cuentan y me dicen que estaba en vías
Or rather that he was thinking about it that he
O sea que que lo estaba pensando que
had made the decision and that he was going to get
había tomado la decisión y que se iba a
divorced I don't know I met a man
divorciar yo no lo sé yo di con un señor
who wanted me to marry me
que él me quería para casarse conmigo
to have children to be his wife
para tener hijos para ha serer su esposa
who wants to believe it, let them believe it
que quiera creérselo que se lo crea el
who doesn't, let them not believe it because it doesn't matter to me
que no que no se lo crea que a mí me da
Exactly the same but
Exactamente igual pero
seeing the character well it wouldn't have
viendo el personaje pues no me hubiera
surprised me if over time she
extrañado que con el tiempo se se
had gotten divorced the truth is I was
hubiera divorciada la verdad yo me quedé
widowed at 27 years old gentlemen I lost the love
viuda con 27 años señores perdí al amor
of my life that was the love of my life
de mi vida ese sí fue el amor de mi vida
I have been able to have  many loves each
yo he podido tener muchos amores cada
love is
amor es
different Do you think they would have
distinto Tú crees que se hubieran
divorced Marina
divorciado Marina
m of course it's that that's something that
m claro es que es que eso es algo que
nobody can hear me well
nadie puede se me escucha bien
yes the stop is pending No let's see there's
sí la parada está pendiente No a ver
one left I have one left eh it's that it's something
queda una me queda una eh es que es algo
so subjective if they had divorced
tan subjetivo si se hubieran divorciado
No but of course since he's going to say ugh What a
No pero claro ya que va a decir buf Qué
look It's that I can't help it
mirada Es que es que no puedo evitarlo
what I wanted Pantoja didn't eh but it
lo deseado el Pantoja no me eh pero
's always like I was left a widow I was
siempre es como yo me quedé viuda yo me
left a widow I was left a widow eh [ __ ] and that they
quedé viuda yo me quedé viuda eh y
shared so-called little
eso que compartieron entre comillas poco
time what will people who have been there
tiempo que dirá la gente que ha estado
20 30 40 years say, I mean I think
20 30 40 años o sea creo que
obviously the pain eh You shouldn't
evidentemente el dolor eh No hay que
judge anyone's pain but man
juzgar el dolor de nadie pero hombre
carrying the
cargar
widow of Spain for years I think thato No no let's
años con la viuda de España creo queo No
go evident Lu right her life was
no vamos evident Lu recho su vida tenía
27 years old her whole life ahead of her well
27 años toda la vida por delante bueno
not a
no esa un
second [ __ ] that I live because
segundo que vivo porque es que
vatela let's have lived there without
vatela vamos habber vivido yo allí sin
knowing how to talk to anyone it would have
saber hablar con nadie es que hubiera
been a pain Fat wait now I know
sido una putada Gorda ya espera Ya sé
the train is salting Forgive
que está salando el tren Perdona a la
people Eh but now  we're arriving my goodness the
gente Eh pero ya estamos llegando madre
people who don't listen to me one
mía la gente que no que escúchame una
thing is that here I believe that to live you
cosa es que aquí yo creo que para vivir
have to be worth it because it's
hay que valer porque es que uno hace
so cold there are no people there's no there's no
mucho frío la gente no hay no hay no hay
human warmth there's no hug there's no there's no there's no
calidez humana no hay abrazo no hay no
closeness you understand me
hay no hay cercanía tú me entiendes
right Javi Yes I know that you
verdad Javi Yo sí yo sé que a ti te
really like contact Well yes son
gusta mucho el contacto Pues sí hijo es
let's see hugs generate
que vamos a ver los abrazos generan
oxytocin adrenaline they're necessary son
oxitocina adrenalina son necesarios hijo
if it were up to you I don't know all day you
si por ti fuera no sé todo el día que
would be all day fighting with the
estarías todo el día peleado con el
world well no we have to hug love each other
mundo pues no hay que abrazarse quererse
love each other a little yeah eh There are people who are
amarse un poco sí eh Hay gente que es
very there are people who are very disgusting let's
muy hay gente que da mucho
see but where are you Tell me what's your
purco a ver pero dónde estás Cuéntame
name is your name yes where is it let's see tell me
cómo se llamao se llama si dónde está a
mat dorfer let's see tell me where you
ver dímelo mat dorfer a ver dime dónde
are in
estás en
mat and now let's see dear
mat y ahora vamos a a ver querido
languages dear I have no idea the truth
idiomas querido No ni idea la verdad
So now we have to go down the people
Entonces ahora hay que bajar la gente
are silent that's very strange anything is worth I'll
está en silencio eso rarísimo todo vale
put a video Go out from there no no you
pongo vídeo Ve saliendo de ahí no no tú
Come on yes no But I can tell you
Dale si no Pero yo te puedo contar
many things eh on the way do you want to
muchas cosas eh por el camino quieres
put a video
poner vídeo
eh we'll finish it we'll finish it  Yes go ahead
eh lo terminamos lo terminamos Sí dale
but that was the love of my life
dale pero ese fue el amor de mi vida
until I died Because that's why I have
hasta que me muera Porque por eso yo no
never remarried,
me he vuelto a casar nunca
that he does not respect the last wish of
que no respeta el último deseo de
supposedly someone who loves
supuestamente alguien que quiere
supposedly is that he does not love you or in other words you do
supuestamente es que no te quiere o sea
not believe that he loved your
que no crees que quisiera a tu
father, he did not want your father this is a
padre no quería tu padre esto
lie my opinion if someone gets offended I am so
mentira mi opinión si alguien se ofende
sorry do you think he has respected
Lo siento mucho crees que ha respetado
the memory of your father for anything public
la memoria de tu padre para nada público
and
y
notorious do you want to defir he
notorio quieres defir
has our things that belong to us
tiene nuestras cosas que nos pertenece
from my father they are Personal Effects that
de mi padre son Efectos Personales que
have no economic value but they
no tiene ningún valor económico pero
have an incalculable personal value
tiene un valor personal incalculable
and come on we would love it now I don't know if we
y vamos nos encantaría ya no sé si si
can continue dreaming about it but it
podemos seguir soñando con ello pero
is clear that we would love to
está claro que nos encantaría poder
have it someday do you think that I will
tenerlo algún día crees que recuperaré
one day recover those belongings of your father it would be
algún día esos enseres de tu padre sería
a huge surprise it would be a
una sorpresa enorme sería una sorpresa
huge surprise and it would be wonderful at
enorme y y sería maravilloso por lo
least to be able to give my children something from their
menos puer darle algo a mis hijos de su
grandfather but I have no faith and
abuelo pero no tengo ninguna fe y
no trust at least
ninguna confianza por lo menos
while certain people are alive
mientras mientras ciertas personas vivan
if those people die God willing they
si esas personas mueren que Dios quiera
live a long time Eh well I don't know
que vivan mucho tiempo Eh pues ya no lo
and those certain people are apart from
sé y esas ciertas personas son aparte de
Isabel Pantoja another one that is
Isabel Pantoja otro que hay por ahí
around there goes I am with  he Until he
alrededor va Yo estoy con él Hasta que
goes to the square when he leaves I pray and I
se va a la plaza cuando se marcha rezo y
wait for them to call me
espero a que me llamen de cada toro
from the square for each bull and you usually go when
desde la plaza y sueles ir cuando torea
he's fighting no never And why don't I
él no nunca Y por qué no
feel a very strange thing inside
siento una cosita muy extraña dentro de
me I'm really scared of my mother How
m Me da muchísimo miedo mi madre Que
beautiful how young
guapa que joven
Not the other person a horror could
No la otra persona un horror podr
forgive What harm could I do to her when she
perdonar Qué daño le pued hacer cuando
was 10 years old my brother who had that
tenía 10 años mi hermano que tenía s ese
harm that he did to us I can't forget
daño que nos hizo yo no lo puedo olvar
no
nun
forgiveness my position is very
perdon mi posicionamiento lo tengo
clear it's funny that we agree
clarísimo tiene gra que coincidamos
because it's true that as
porque sí que es verdad que como dice
our friend Olga says who sent us the
nuestra amiga Olga que nos ha mandado el
audio normally the meetings of the
audio normalmente las reuniones de de
content outline of the television it's not
escaleta de contenidos de la tele no es
that they tell you it's not that they tell you stand
que te digan no es que te digan ponte
here stand there stand there no but it
aquí Ponte tú allí Ponte tú allí no pero
's true Hey well how I
sí que es verdad Oye pues que cómo os
tell you there's no kind of
digo no tiene gracia ningún tipo de
grace that everyone goes to the same there has to be
Gracia que todos vayan a la misma tiene
a debate all the people
que haber un debate todas la gente se
feel identified with each other and you
siente identificada con unos con otros y
play a little no no we're not going to
juegas un poco no no vamos a pensar
always think the same because if not but it's
siempre igual porque si no pero sí que
true that it's that here my mother
es verdad que es que aquí madre mía
boy I mean eh  It's out of hate and
chico o sea eh es por odio y por
revenge but that's what he
venganza pero es lo que él dice
really says What a good location I have eh I haven't even
realmente Qué buena ubicación tengo eh
looked at the GPS or anything I'm here for
ni he miro el GPS ni nada Yo aquí por
good arriving at my house I see you no
biena llegando a mi casa te veo no
eh but it's really like that how how
eh pero realmente es eso cómo cómo
can you say that you want and that you love and
puedes decir que quieres y que amas y
that has been the love of your life if the
que ha sido el amor de tu vida si los
loves of your life of your of your
amores de tu vida de tu de tu
widower you are not capable of giving them the
viudo tú no eres capaz de darles el
place that they deserve giving them those
lugar que se merecen dándoles esos
objects I mean it's ad impression that they
objetos o sea es que es ad impresion que
are things that let's
son cosas que
see your son is going to keep some
a ver tu hijo se va a quedar con unas
things you with others and his other children with
cosas tú con otras y sus otros hijos con
others in each one with what
otras en cada uno con lo que le
corresponds to them or with what that's why our
corresponda o con lo que por eso nuestra
friend Olga Lidia our friend Olga what the
amiga Olga Lidia nuestra amiga Olga có
[ __ ] I mean how the hell does she justify something like that
o sea como narices justifica algo
If she has to she can
así Si es que tiene que lo puede
justify it because it's really
justificar porque es que realmente es
like out of resentment, out of rage, out of hate Because I do
como por rencor por rabia por odio Por
n't know it's like a person who is not
no sé es como una persona que no es
happy who is never happy who doesn't pretend
feliz que nunca es feliz que no hace
that they don't like the good of others, the
como que no le gusta el bien ajeno el el
sharing, I really tell you eh
compartir el yo de verdad te lo digo eh
And as an artist she is spectacular if
Y como artista es que es espectacular si
one thing doesn't take away from the other I do
es que una cosa no quita para la otra yo
n't  I can understand Javi, I really
no lo puedo entender Javi de verdad te
tell you living like this but of course you tell me
lo digo vivir así pero claro tú me dices
that on the set there are always people
lo de que en el plató siempre hay gente
who are on one side and people who are
que está para un lado y gente que está
on the other, of course it's not like that yes although
para el otro claro no es así sí aunque
eye eye eye although you don't think like that eh I have
ojo ojo ojo aunque no pienses así eh yo
seen people well we already know it is that there is
he visto gente bueno ya lo sabemos es
no more than I have friends and
que no hay más que yo tengo amigos y
acquaintances that I know perfectly well what they
conocidos que sé perfectamente lo que
think on certain topics and that they know
piensan determinados temas y que saben
what they have to say and what not To be
que lo que tienen que decir y lo que no
or not to be and I know it because
Para estar o no estar y lo sé porque lo
we have talked about it outside, I mean then there are
hemos hablado fuera o sea entonces hay
people who go through it and there are people that we
gente que pasa por eso y hay gente que
don't go through or I mean each one is as they are, that's it,
no pasamos o sea cada uno es como es ya
there are people who take it as a
está hay gente que se lo toma como un
game because it really is a game and there are
juego porque realmente es un juego y hay
people Well, well there are certain things that
gente Pues que bueno hay ciertas cosas
well it's not that you don't know I ca
que pues que no es que que no sabes yo
n't talk it's an example okay I'm
no puedo hablar es un ejemplo vale Te
going to give you an example I can't say
voy a poner un ejemplo yo no puedo decir
eh Terel Ampos I think what
eh terel ampos Me parece maravilloso lo
Alejandra Rubio has done is wonderful it's that it's
que ha hecho Alejandra Rubio es que es
spectacular it's that I'm not sorry I'm
espectacular es que no lo siento me
left without 200 and perfect really I'll go somewhere
quedo sin 200 y perfecto de verdad iré a
else I mean there are no
otro lado o sea
things that there are no people you know it
no hay cosas que no hay gente sabes
seems silly But in the end no
parece una tontería Pero al final no que
No, no, I'm really telling you, no, you
no que no De verdad te lo digo no tú me
understand me, right? Yes, but what I don't
comprendes verdad sí pero lo que yo no
understand is, or rather, what I want to know is
comprendo es o sea lo que quiero saber
the people who have taken
la gente que se ha puesto de parte
her side, what have the people who have
de de ella qué ha dicho la gente que se
taken Isabel Pantoja's side said? That the
ha puesto de parte de Isabel Pantoja que
scoundrel, once again the only
que Sinvergüenza que otra vez el único
argument that there is to be said, the scoundrel,
argumento que hay que que Sinvergüenza
once again to make money, that he
que otra vez a rentabilizar que ya no
has nothing and once again tells the same thing which
tiene nada y cuenta otra vez lo mismo
is true, that he once again tells the
que es verdad que cuenta otra vez lo
same thing, that he needs money like another
mismo que necesita dinero que otro
starving man hanging, and Pantoja, that the
muerto de hambre colgado yel Pantoja que
poor thing, that everyone else is
que pobrecita que todo el mundo que es
the easy resource, that she really is like that,
el recurso fácil que en verdad es así
but that doesn't take away from it, well, we're back to the
pero eso no le quita pues volvemos a lo
same thing Javi, talking about an issue,
mismo Javi el hablar de un tema
eh? Let's see how I can explain it to you, okay,
eh A ver cómo te lo explico vale el
talking about an issue that everyone
hablar de un tema que del que todos
says one thing about, in this case everyone or it
dicen una cosa en este caso todos o
seems that, for a month there are a series
parece que Durante un mes hay una serie
of testimonies that go against that makes you think that
de testimonios que van en contra eso te
my testimony or that the
hace que ese testimonio mío o que el
fact that it is, how can I explain it to you,
hecho de que esté cómo te lo explico le
takes away its veracity, the fact that 30 are
quita veracidad el hecho de que vayan 30
against it, I mean, it's like the fact that she is
en contra o sea es como el hecho de que
portraying her as a victim, is that  I don't know
la ponga como una víctima es que no sé
how to tell you it's like when you tell something
cómo decirte es como cuando cuentas algo
here maybe you can make a mistake on
aquí a lo mejor te puedes equivocar en
the day in such a way it really takes away
el día en la forma tal le quita
veracity from what you're
realmente veracidad a lo que estás
saying or or it's like they grab on
contando o o es como que se agarran en
instead of in Yes to Fran's message
vez de en Sí al mensaje de Fran a otra
again you're capitalizing on it they divert they
vez lo estás rentabilizando desvían
divert the subject you know what I want to
desvían el tema sabes lo que te quiero
tell you because they don't have arguments to
decir porque no tienen argumentos para
justify something like that but let's see I say
justificar algo así pero a ver digo a lo
maybe there is and some way to justify
mejor hay y alguna manera de justificar
and I don't see it and I like listening to
y yo no la veo y a mí me gusta escuchado
opinions precisely because maybe
opiniones precisamente porque a lo mejor
someone takes it and says man is that what you're
alguien coge y dice hombre es que lo que
not seeing is that eh Isabel or Kiko
no estás viendo Es que eh Isabel o Kiko
but of course It's that here the so much look
pero claro Es que aquí la tanto mira
here what there is is Carmina saying it
aquí lo que hay es Carmina diciéndolo
the children saying it and Kiko Rivera
los hijos diciéndolo y Kiko Rivera
when he fights with the mother saying
cuando se pelea con la madre contando
that he is torto rigged clear There's no
que se encuentra tor tinglado claro No
way no this is a disgusting thing
hay manera no esto es una asquerosidad
that Isabel Pantoja is doing one more of
que está haciendo Isabel Pantoja una más
course Yes but of course but for Yes of course
claro Sí pero claro pero para Sí claro
but for the fanatic people the people who
pero para la gente fanática la gente que
admire her as an artist who love her who
la admira como artista que la ama que la
venerate her that it is
que la venera que la es que es
inconceivable because they feel attacked
inconcebible porque se sienten atacados
they themselves are like attacking
ellos mismos es como estáis atacando a
my idol fpadm you can hear the traffic lights
mi ídola fpadm se oyen los semáforos
here let's see if people listen to this look
aquí a ver si la gente Escucha esto mira
Ah well Hi and in Spain they are heard like
Ah bueno Hi y En España se escuchan como
the beep for the deaf
el pitido para los sordos
no Clear but I don't know no no but for the
no Claro pero no sé no no pero para los
deaf it's not that this is not like strange I don't
sordos no es que esto no es como raro no
know no no it doesn't look like it's for it
sé no no tiene pinta que sea para lo
only looks like it's some mechanism
solo tiene pinta que sea algún mecanismo
that is sounding and you can hear it because
que esté sonando y se escucha porque
the street is
está la calle en
silent you who are here to know it
silencio tú que estás aquí para saberlo
no But because man yes yes for yes yes
no Pero porque hombre si si para si si
apart from for the deaf it wouldn't be It would be
aparte para los sordos no sería Sería
for the blind I'm an idiot dude I'm
para los ciegos Soy gilipolla tío soy
stupid no
tonto no